Guide to the Larry Kramer Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- October 2008 Acquisition, circa 1916-2008; 100.38; (116 boxes) + 2 broadside folders, 8 rolls, 2 record albums
  - Writings, circa 1937-2005
    - Shorter Works and Other Writings
      - "The Abbots" and "The Lady and the Hard Hat" (Box 105)
      - "Adam and Company", circa 1971 (Box 105)
      - "The Big Three at Yalta", circa 1970s; 13 (Box 105)
      - "The Big Three at Yalta", circa 1970s; 2 (Box 106)
      - "Create Yourself A New Image, Charlie", circa 1965 (Box 106)
      - "Day of Atonement", circa 1981; 11 (Box 106)
      - "The Department Store", circa 1969; 2 (Box 106)
      - "Do Two Dead Homosexuals Equal One Dead Prostitute?", circa 1981 (Box 107)
      - "Envelope scrap" (Box 107)
      - "Early Writings [poetry and prose]", circa 1957- (Box 107)
      - "Fear Comedy and Larry -Ellen 16c" (Box 107)
      - "Freshman Year", 3 (Box 107)
      - "A Gambol Off the Deep End", circa 1956 (Box 107)
      - "Journal of the Plague Years", circa 1987 (Box 107)
      - "LA notes and story notecards" (Box 107)
      - "The Lady and the Hard Hat", circa 1973 (Box 107)
      - "The Ladies who Lunch", circa 1971; 6 (Box 107)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 107)
      - Miscellaneous poems (Box 107)
      - "Mrs. Tefillin", circa 1980s (Box 107)
      - "Mrs. Tefillin", circa 1980s-1996; 11 (Box 108)
      - "Only Yesterday" (Box 108)
      - "The Sexual Education of an American Male", circa 1979; 2 (Box 108)
      - Various, circa 1978-1980 (Box 108)
      - Unidentified Manuscript, 2 (Box 108)
  - Writing Files, circa 1968-2004
    This series consists of material relating to the production, publication, and reception of Kramer's writings (including plays, screenplays, and books). Material includes correspondence, press material, clippings, reviews, royalty statements, notes, and photographs. For material relating more to the creation of Kramer's writings, see Writings, Drafts and Manuscripts.
    - "BBC 'Arena' documentary on Larry Kramer", circa 1990s (Box 109)
    - The Destiny of Me, circa1990-1993; 16 (Box 109)
    - The Destiny of Me, circa 1992-1997; 18 (Box 110)
      Includes photographic slides.
    - Faggots, circa 1978-1979; 4 (Box 110)
    - Faggots, circa 1979-1995; 9 (Box 111)
    - "First Hero", circa 1994 (Box 111)
    - "Freshman Year" (Box 111)
    - Just Say No: A Play about a Farce, circa 1988-1989; 2 (Box 111)
    - Just Say No: A Play about a Farce, circa 1988-1995; 13 (Box 112)
    - "Kramer biography", circa 1995 (Box 112)
    - "Kramer vs. Kramer", circa 1989 (Box 112)
    - "Marvin's Room", circa 1992 (Box 112)
    - Mass, Larry, circa 1996-1997 (Box 112)
    - "Noel and Cole", circa 1995 (Box 112)
    - The Normal Heart, circa 1982-1985; 19 (Box 113)
    - The Normal Heart, circa 1985-1986; 14 (Box 114)
    - The Normal Heart, circa 1985-1988; 13 (Box 115)
    - The Normal Heart, circa 1986-1990s; 15 (Box 116)
    - The Normal Heart, circa 1991-1997; 16 (Box 117)
      Includes two audiocassettes of "The Normal Heart" (circa 1993).
      Access to original audiocassettes is restricted. Reference copies may be requested.
    - "Notes and Photos", circa 1995; 5 (Box 117)
    - "Penguin Book of Gay Short Fiction", circa 1993; 2 (Box 117)
    - Reports From the Holocaust, circa 1989-1990s; 16 (Box 118)
    - "Sissies' Scrapbook", circa 1975; 2 (Box 118)
    - Women in Love, circa 1967-1971; 25 (Box 119)
    - Women in Love, circa 1968-2004; 5 (Box 120)
  - Professional Papers and Research Material, circa 1950s-2006
    This series consists of a wide range of material relating broadly to Kramer's various professional activities, including his film work, his AIDS advocacy and activism, especially his work with Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) and AIDS Coalition to Unleash Power (ACT UP), and his non-literary writing. Material includes correspondence, printed material, notes and notebooks, research material, typescripts of articles and speeches, clippings of interviews and articles by and about Kramer, and other office files.
    Organized into eight groupings: Notebooks; Film Project Files; Early Files; AIDS General; AIDS Activism; Research Material; Interviews, Articles, and Speeches; and Other Files.
    Within the groupings, files are not arranged in any particular order.
    - Notebooks
      - Notebooks, circa 1970s; 13 (Box 121)
    - Film Project Files
      - Outline, circa 1980 (Box 122)
      - Film Articles, circa 1969 (Box 122)
      - Variety, circa 1971 (Box 122)
      - Film Correspondence, circa 1972-1973 (Box 122)
      - Women in Love, circa 1967-1971; 24 (Box 122)
      - Forbidden Colors, circa 1968-1971; 12 (Box 123)
      - Lost Horizon, circa 1971-1973; 5 (Box 124)
      - Mo Rothman's Production Report, circa 1960-1961 (Box 124)
      - Photographs - Larry Kramer (Box 124)
      - Film Notebooks (Box 124)
      - Film - Miscellaneous printed (Box 124)
      - "Transatlantic View", article for Publisher's Weekly, circa 1966; 2 (Box 124)
      - Late Bloomers, circa 1980-1982 (Box 124)
      - St. Krebs, proposed TV comedy, circa 1982 (Box 124)
      - Beautiful and the Damned, film project, circa 1969-1971 (Box 124)
      - Columbia Sudios Film Proposals, circa 1956-1965 (Box 124)
      - "Ideas", circa 1971 (Box 124)
      - "Americans in England" (Box 124)
      - Albermarle Productions, Women in Love, circa 1968-1969; 4 (Box 124)
      - "U A Cross-Collateralisation", Women in Love (Box 124)
      - "Moving Day", circa 1973 (Box 124)
      - Financial, circa 1980s; 2 (Box 125)
      - De Stael Project, circa 1971 (Box 125)
      - "Possible Projects", correspondence, circa 1970 (Box 125)
      - "III", circa 1976 (Box 125)
      - "Stay Hungry", research, circa 1972 (Box 125)
      - "The Color of Money", correspondence (Box 125)
    - Early Files
      - Student papers, circa 1952-1955 (Box 125)
      - Portrait photos, circa 1950s (Box 125)
      - Resume and job applications, circa 1950s (Box 125)
      - Kamp Kohut yearbooks and High School and College commencement programs, circa 1950-1957 (Box 125)
      - Financial, circa 1950s (Box 125)
      - Will, circa 1972 (Box 125)
      - Correspondence, circa 1966-1969 (Box 125)
      - Clippings, 1968 (Box 125)
      - Personal (Box 125)
      - Marrakech, circa 1969 (Box 125)
      - Family Correspondence, circa 1960 (Box 125)
      - "N.Y." (Box 125)
      - Clippings, circa 1960s (Box 125)
      - Notes, circa 1970 (Box 125)
      - Correspondence - Fifield, Barringer, circa 1970-1972 (Box 126)
      - Correspondence - Greenstein, Martin, circa 1972 (Box 126)
      - Correspondence - Caricatures, circa 1966 (Box 126)
      - "Bob Damron's Address Book", circa 1971 (Box 126)
      - "Journal to Journal", fragments, circa 1971-1972 (Box 126)
      - Photo portraits, circa 1973 (Box 126)
      - "Parties" (Box 126)
      - "Humor" (Box 126)
      - Topical - Loeb Drama Center, Harvard, circa 1971-1976 (Box 126)
      - Scotland, circa 1970s (Box 126)
      - Clippings, circa 1960s-1970s; 2 (Box 126)
      - Op-Ed piece, regarding Harvey Milk, circa 1978 (Box 126)
      - Yale 25th Reunion article (Box 126)
      - "Dog paperwork", circa 1979-1980 (Box 126)
      - Press clippings, circa 1969-1970; 2 (Box 126)
      - "To Sleep Til Tuesday", circa 1953 (Box 126)
      - "Astrological", circa 1974 (Box 126)
      - "Whore House", planned novel, circa 1979 (Box 126)
      - "Is Homosexuality a Form?," New School for Social Research Course, circa 1980; 2 (Box 126)
      - Loose Letters, circa 1980; 2 (Box 126)
    - AIDS General
      - AIDS, miscellaneous correspondence, circa 1993; 3 (Box 127)
      - Community Research Initiative (Box 127)
      - Darrell Yates Rist (Box 127)
      - Salk Institute (Box 127)
      - Royal Marks Foundation (Box 127)
      - The Advocate, circa 1990s; 7 (Box 127)
      - Project Inform, circa 1995 (Box 128)
      - Lamda, circa 1994 (Box 128)
      - Broadway Cares, circa 1994 (Box 128)
      - TAG, circa 1995 (Box 128)
      - Political Writings, circa 1990-1991 (Box 128)
      - General Interest, circa 1989-1992 (Box 128)
      - AIDS, circa 1991-1993 (Box 128)
      - Future Direction in AIDS Research, circa 1993 (Box 128)
      - Hepatitis, circa 1991 (Box 128)
      - Time, circa 1983-1993 (Box 128)
      - Misc Letters regarding AIDS, circa 1994-1997 (Box 128)
      - POZ, circa 1994-1997 (Box 128)
      - GMHC (Gay Men's Health Crisis), circa 1995 (Box 128)
      - PWA, circa 1996 (Box 128)
      - ACT UP, circa 1993-1994 (Box 128)
      - D.P.N., circa 1994 (Box 128)
      - Common Cause, circa 1996; 3 (Box 128)
      - Larry Kramer - Miscellaneous writings, circa 1989-1990 (Box 128)
      - Philadelphia, the movie (1994), circa 1994; 4 (Box 129)
      - "Other Authors", circa 1995; 4 (Box 129)
    - AIDS Activism
      - Gay Men's Heath Crisis, circa 1983-1991; 7 (Box 129)
        Includes an award - an engraved metal tray - given to Larry Kramer by the Gay Men's Health Crisis.
      - ACT UP, circa 1990-1991; 7 (Box 129)
      - ACT UP, circa 1990-1991; 20 (Box 130)
      - ACT UP, circa 1990s; 2 (Box 131)
    - Research Material
      - Research Material, 2 (Box 131)
        Includes clippings, printed material, and notes pertaining to various subjects, including Roy Cohn and Proust.
      - Research Material, 25 (Box 132)
    - Interviews, Articles, and Speeches
      - Medical writings - AIDS (Box 132)
      - New York Times, correspondence and clippings, circa 1988-1993; 4 (Box 133)
      - Out Week, correspondence and clippings, circa 1990 (Box 133)
      - Ed Koch, correspondence and clippings, circa 1989-1990 (Box 133)
      - New York Native, circa 1989 (Box 133)
      - Village Voice, circa 1989 (Box 133)
      - "Articles for The Advocate", circa 1991-1995 (Box 133)
      - "Article, A Good News / Bad News AIDS Joke", circa 1996 (Box 133)
      - Interviews of and Articles by Larry Kramer, 11 (Box 133)
      - AIDS: The War is Lost, circa 1990 (Box 133)
      - Architectural Digest, Feature on Larry Kramer, circa 1995; 2 (Box 134)
      - Science Magazine letter (Box 134)
      - Transmission, circa 1996 (Box 134)
      - Key West Literary Seminar (Box 134)
      - America Academy of Arts and Letters, Award, circa 1996; 2 (Box 134)
      - Writers Contract, "The New AIDS Crisis", circa 1997 (Box 134)
      - Current biography, circa 1994 (Box 134)
      - ICM (letter to prospective agent), circa 1996 (Box 134)
      - Interviews, circa 1993-1994 (Box 134)
      - New York Public Library, correspondence regarding manuscript collection, circa 1992-1993 (Box 134)
      - Quotes, correspondence, circa 1995-1996 (Box 134)
      - Rudin, Scott - correspondence, circa 1996-1997 (Box 134)
      - Writing Requests, circa 1997 (Box 134)
      - Speeches, circa 1991-1993; 3 (Box 134)
      - Speech notes (Box 134)
      - Memorials, circa 1993-1994 (Box 134)
      - Lectures, 5 (Box 134)
      - GMHC: Interview with Larry Kramer, transcript, circa 1994 (Box 135)
      - New York magazine, Larry Kramer interview, circa 1998 (Box 135)
      - Albany Speech, circa 2000 (Box 135)
        Includes a transcript of a speech, delivered by Larry Kramer in 1994 and electronically annotated by Kramer in 2000.
      - The Advocate, letters to editor regarding Larry Kramer article, circa 1997 (Box 135)
      - Notebook, Gay essays (Box 135)
      - Writing, "The Bloods" (Box 135)
      - Writing, "The Redfern Document" (Box 135)
      - "Nuremberg Trials for AIDS", circa 2006 (Box 135)
      - Notebook, "First Lady, or See America First" (Box 135)
      - Notebook, "Old Age" (Box 135)
    - Other Files
      - Notebook - Dawidowicz in commentary, Asylum (Box 135)
      - AIDS Treatment Activists Conference Binder, circa 1990 (Box 135)
      - Larry Kramer Initiative, Yale University, circa 1996-1997; 5 (Box 135)
      - The Destiny of Me, Reviews, circa 2002 (Box 136)
      - Filofax pages, circa 2004 (Box 136)
      - Printed, AIDS-related, 2 (Box 136)
      - Miscellaneous notes and writings (Box 136)
      - Appointment Calendar, circa 2004-2005 (Box 136)
      - Lesbian and Gay Studies at Yale, circa 2005; 2 (Box 136)
      - Filofax, circa 2006 (Box 136)
      - Name Tags (Box 136)
      - Rolodex (rotating index), circa 1970s-1980s (Box 137)
      - Kramer computer disks, accompanying documentation (Box 136)
  - Personal and Other Papers, circa 1925-2003
    Organized into six groupings: Family Papers; Household Papers; Medical Records; Other Papers; Printed Material; and Photographs.
    - Family Papers
      Includes material relating to Kramer's family, including his mother Rea, his father George, and his brother Arthur.
      - Album
      - Art Prints
      - "The Brecky 1944", yearbook and photographs, circa 1944 (Box 138)
      - Certificates, Arthur Kramer / 1916 Class Reunion photograph, George Kramer, circa 1950s-1960s
      - Certificates, Rea Kramer, circa 1920s-1930s
      - Clippings (Box 138)
      - "Death of George L. Kramer", circa 1968; 3 (Box 138)
      - Diary, circa 1933 (Box 138)
      - Diary, "My Trip to the West Coast", circa 1947 (Box 138)
      - Diary, "Incl. 'Death in Positano...' ", circa 1970 (Box 138)
      - "Diplomas, school and Address book" (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Arthur - letterman jacket patch, circa 1944 (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Arthur - Navy Orders, circa 1944 (Box 138)
      - Kramer, George and Rea - "Grand Circle Tour", circa 1964 (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Larry - "Letters to mother", circa 1964-1967 (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Rea (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Rea - letters, circa 1925-1941; 2 (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Rea - Travel documents, 2 (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Rea and George - Letters (Box 139)
      - "Material related to travels", circa 1960s (Box 139)
      - The Onondagan, circa 1925 (Box 139)
      - Papers, loose (Box 139)
      - Photograph Album, 2 (Box 139)
      - Photograph Album - "My Grandchildren" (Box 139)
      - Photographic portraits
      - Photographs, 5 (Box 139)
      - Photographs of Larry and Arthur Kramer (Box 139)
      - Postcards (Box 139)
      - Printed family material (Box 139)
      - "The Sam Hanky Color Code handkerchief " (Box 139)
      - Scrapbook
      - Tefillin, 2 (Box 139)
        Includes the two parts of a tefillin, also known as phylacteries.
      - Yale Class of 1916 - Reunion in Print, circa 1942 (Box 139)
      - Yale Moot Court of Appeals, circa 1951 (Box 139)
    - Household Papers
      - Connecticut expenses (Box 140)
      - Connecticut house (Box 140)
      - Connecticut mortgage, 2 (Box 140)
      - Various, 2 (Box 140)
    - Medical Records
      - A.A.R.P., circa 1994 (Box 140)
      - AETNA Insurance, circa 1990 (Box 140)
      - Blue Choice HMO, circa 1996; 2 (Box 140)
      - Blue Cross, circa 1993-1994; 6 (Box 140)
        Includes radiographs (x-rays).
      - Blue Cross, circa 1993-1995; 5 (Box 141)
      - Caremark, circa 1996 (Box 141)
      - Community Prescription, circa 1995 (Box 141)
      - Health Records, circa 2002-2003; 4 (Box 141)
      - Writers Guild Insurance, circa 1989 (Box 141)
      - X-rays
    - Other Papers
      - Awards
      - Honorary award, The Normal Heart theater event benefiting the Gay Men's Health Crisis
      - Personal mentions, circa 1990s; 10 (Box 141)
      - Personal mentions, circa 1990s; 7 (Box 142)
      - Royalty Earnings, circa 1990s (Box 142)
      - T-Shirts and Hats (Box 143)
    - Printed Material
      - AIDS activism, posters
      - Various speaking events, posters
      - The Destiny of Me, posters
      - Faggots, posters
      - Four Friends, posters
      - The Normal Heart, posters
      - Women in Love, posters
      - The Night Larry Kramer Kissed Me, poster, circa 2000
      - The Tragedy of Today's Gays, poster, circa 2005
      - Rolled posters, unsorted
        Includes posters for movies, plays, and speaking events, as well as ones dealing with AIDS activism.
      - Miscellaneous printed
      - Book, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans who make a Difference, by Barbaralee Diomonstein, circa 1997 (Box 144)
      - Magazines, circa 1949-1990s; 4 (Box 144)
      - Magazines, circa 1980s-2000s; 12 (Box 145)
      - Magazines, circa 1990-2008; 13 (Box 146)
      - Newspapers, circa 1970s-2000s; 5 (Box 147)
      - "Printed Mentions", circa 1989-1993; 6 (Box 147)
      - "Printed Mentions", 4 (Box 148)
    - Photographs
      - Arnold, Eve, circa 1965 (Box 148)
      - "Book Party" (Box 148)
      - Davis, Brad - head shot (Box 148)
      - "Europe" (Box 148)
      - Family photographs, circa 1900s -1980s; 6 (Box 148)
      - Gunderson, Gary - Larry Kramer portrait, circa 1995 (Box 148)
      - Hill, Ethan, circa 2001 (Box 148)
      - Hill, Ethan, circa 2001; 2 (Box 149)
      - Kramer, Larry, 5 (Box 149)
      - Kramer, Larry, by Annie Leibovitz
      - Mulberry Bush (Box 149)
      - Personal photographs, including negatives, circa 1952-1980s; 9 (Box 149)
      - Snapshots and portraits of Larry Kramer, including slides (Box 149)
      - Snapshots and portraits of Larry Kramer, including slides, 4 (Box 150)
      - Various photographs, including negatives, circa 1966; 2 (Box 150)
      - Various slides and negatives, 2 (Box 150)
      - Women in Love, circa 1969; 7 (Box 150)
    - Framed print of the poem "Bore," inscribed "Love, Charlie"
    - Wall mural by Larry Kramer
  - Audiovisual Material, circa 1967-1990s
    Box 233 contains a stand-alone list of what appears to be recorded television segments on Kramer and AIDS-related content. It is not married to a particular video cassette.
    Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Audiocassettes, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 151)
      Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      Includes audio recordings of interviews, meetings, events, and a Simon & Schuster "The Normal Heart" production, as well as unlabelled cassettes with unknown material. Also includes a John Bucchino cassette (circa 1991) called "Solitude Lessons."
      - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889135)
      - "Larry King Show", 1989 April 6; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889143)
      - "Sleep Easy", Summit Counseling Ctr., undated; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889150)
      - "Ride the Chariot", Yale Glee Club, 1987; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889168)
      - Fuch writ re Mayor / Judy Peabody, 1988 January 2; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889176)
      - "Meridian: AIDS in the Arts", 1991 January 22; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889184)
      - John Bucchino, Solitude Lessons, 1991; 1 (Box 151)
        This is a commercial audiocassette. It has not been digitized.
      - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889192)
      - Larry Kramer, BJS, CIS, "Normal Heart", 1994 January 31, February 2-3; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889200)
      - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889218)
      - "The Normal Heart", Act 1, undated; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889226)
      - "The Normal Heart", Act 2, undated; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889234)
      - Radio Free America #16, AIDS: Epidemic or Weapon of War?, Dave Emory, tape 1, 1986 April; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889242)
      - Radio Free America #16, AIDS: Epidemic or Weapon of War?, Dave Emory, tape 2, 1986 April; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889259)
      - Radio Free America #16, AIDS: Epidemic or Weapon of War?, Dave Emory, tape 3, 1986 April; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889267)
      - Radio Free America #16, AIDS: Epidemic or Weapon of War?, Dave Emory, tape 4, 1987 July; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889275)
      - Radio Free America #16, AIDS: Epidemic or Weapon of War?, Dave Emory, tape 5, 1987 July; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889283)
      - Project inform, "Update Town Meeting, Notes from Amsterdam" (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1992 August 26; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889291)
      - Project inform, "Update Town Meeting, Notes from Amsterdam" (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1992 August; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889309)
      - "Remembering Stonewall", undated; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889317)
      - "Defamation", narrated by Harvey Fierstein, undated; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889325)
      - Project inform, "AIDS Treatment Update", 1993 October 29; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889333)
      - Project inform,"Town Meeting", September 29; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889341)
      - "May Update", undated; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889358)
      - "April Town Meeting", undated; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889366)
      - Project inform, "August Town Meeting", undated; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889374)
      - "Berlin Update", undated; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889382)
      - Larry, Astrology, tape #1 (1 of 3 audiocassettes), 1992 September; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889390)
      - Larry, Astrology, tape #2 (2 of 3 audiocassettes), 1992 September; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889408)
      - Larry, Astrology, tape #3 (3 of 3 audiocassettes), 1992 September; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889416)
      - "Ideas", AIDS (#7), CBC Radio, 1989 April; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889424)
      - "Ideas", AIDS (#8), CBC Radio, 1989 May; 1 (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889432)
    - Phonograph records, 45 rpm
      - "Here We Go Round the Mulberry Bush," by Traffic, three copies, circa 1967 (Box 184 (Record Album Storage))
      - Cyril Stapleton and His Orchestra performing "Women in Love," four copies, circa 1970 (Box 185 (Record Album Storage))
    - Audiotape reels, circa 1960s
      - "Women in Love", tape 1, copy 2, #1 to #6, undated; 1 (Box 186, Item barcode 39002104889119)
      - "Women in Love", tape 2, copy 2, #7 to #14, undated; 1 (Box 186, Item barcode 39002104889127)
    - Videocassettes, circa 1980s-1990s
      Includes video recordings of "The Normal Heart", a four-part documentary "A Time of AIDS," Charlie Rose interviews (circa 1990s), and various other interviews and events.
      - Gay Pride '93, Jonathan Hardary intro to Larry Kramer (49 sec.), 1993; YCALMSS722_0001; 1; 00:30:18 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337509)
      - Living Proof: HIV and the Pursuit of Happiness, seventh rough cut, no sound work, 1993 May 24; YCALMSS722_0002; 1; 01:10:00; A timecode run through the entire tape. (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337517)
      - Out in America, Lovett Productions, Inc., WNET-Thirteen, one hour, 1991 June 26; YCALMSS722_0003; 1; 00:59:18 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337525)
      - A Time of AIDS: I. The Zero Factor, undated; YCALMSS722_0004; 1; 01:02:03 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337533)
      - A Time of AIDS: II. Hunting the Virus, undated; YCALMSS722_0005; 1; 01:02:52 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337541)
      - A Time of AIDS: III. Fighting for Life, undated; YCALMSS722_0006; 1; 01:01:59 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337558)
      - A Time of AIDS: IV. The End of the Beginning, undated; YCALMSS722_0007; 1; 00:16:21 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337566)
      - Charlie Rose interview with Larry Kramer, 1993 April 5; YCALMSS722_0008; 1; 00:57:49 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337574)
      - Charlie Rose interview with Larry Kramer, 1993 August 10; YCALMSS224_0002; 1; 01:02:06 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337582)
      - Charlie Rose interview with Larry Kramer, 1995 January 18; YCALMSS722_0010; 1; 00:18:15 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337590)
      - Larry Kramer speech at the AIDS Institute Conference, Albany, 1993 November 14; YCALMSS722_0011; 1; 00:36:25 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337608)